watch-football-online.tv 2009-12-07

# Watch-football-online.tv - Watch Live Football directly on your PC

_Effective April 1, 2007_

**Privacy Policy**

TVProcessing provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of TVProcessing sites. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through our Sites. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes.   
As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on acomputer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within the United States or internationally. 

**Information Collection and Use**

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our services, features and content, to administer your Membership (together, the “ **Service** ”) and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site.  We also may also use your information in order to better understand how our Site and Service are used.

_Personally Identifiable Information._

\- When you register with us through the Site, as a Member or when you choose to create your own profile webpage we will ask you for personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that when on its own or in combination with other identifiers can be used to contact or identify you (“ **Personal Information** ”). Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, email address and postal address. We use your Personal Information mainly to provide the Service and administer your inquiries. 

\- We also collect the other information that you provide as part of registration and the administration and personalization of your profile webpage (e.g., without limitation zip code and individual preferences) (“ **Non-Identifying Information** ”). Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be identified. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your viewing preferences). We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Users to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Service and to analyze and understand how our Site and Service are used. 

\- We also may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. Members who agree to the terms and conditions of the TVProcessing Terms of Service Agreement are given the opportunity to opt into receiving such communications from us in the future. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or update your “user preferences” information. (See “ **Changing or Deleting Information** ,” below.) 

_Log Data._ When you visit the Site, whether as a Member or a non-registered user just browsing, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“ **Log Data** ”). This log data may include information such as your computer’s IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and the Service and for the Site’s technical administration. We do not treat Log Data as Personal Information or use it in association with other Personal Information, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information for the same purposes as stated above regarding other Non-Identifying Information.

**Cookies**

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Site. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage by Users and web traffic routing on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Service. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

_Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information._ We may share aggregated information which does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any such aggregated information will not contain your Personal Information. 

_Service Providers._ We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Site’s features), or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Service are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.  
_Business Transfers._ TVProcessing may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. If TVProcessing becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, reorganization or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice to you before your Personal Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

**Changing or Deleting Your Information**

All Members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their registration profile by contacting us. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your record in our system, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request. See below for privacy contact information. 

**Security & International Transfer **

TVProcessing is very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction  
We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored Personal Data (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Site contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by “clicking on” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third-party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. This Privacy Policy addresses the use and disclosure of information that we collect from you through this Site. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

**Our Policy Toward Children**

This Site is not directed to children under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us
